Tanmay Bharambe

📳 9405404327 | 💌 bharambetr2002@gmail.com | 🕟 github.com/bharambetr2002 | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/tanmaybharambe

Personal Profile

Hello, I'm a technologist with some experience in Android development and Web development, having a keen interest in startup markets, business functions, and investment. I'm a curious learner, a researcher, and an adventurer. To add to that, I enjoy public speaking, logical thinking, and volunteering. Striving strong connections to engage with and bond with in order to contribute to the welfare of mankind as a whole. Always open for collaboration and mentoring.

Education

Gokhale Education Society's R. H. Sapat College of Engineering and Research

Nashik, India

Bachlor of Computer Engineering

July 2020 - June 2024

· Courses: Data Structures and Algorithm, Object Oriented Programming, Computer Graphics, Theory of Computation, Database, Computer Networks, Cloud Computing, Discrete Mathematics, Microprocessor,

Matoshri Jr. College, Eklahare, Nashik

Nashik, India

HSC

SSC

Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

Graduated

Boys Town Public School

Nashik, India

Feb 2017 - Feb 2018

- Passed with Distinction
- · Specialised in Physics, Chemistry, Maths and Technical

Work Experience_

Google Developers Students Club

GESCOE, Nashik

Co-Lead

Sept 2021 - Current

- Conducted Compose camp under the Academic year 2022-2023 where we had almost 400+ participants for online session and 250+ attendees for Android Workshop
- Responsible for Smooth functioning of the club.
- · Connected more than 800+ Students to GDSC during my Tenure of Being Outreach Lead.
- Technical Skills: Android Development, Web Development
- · Soft Skills: Teamwork, Event Management Skills, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills

Lumos Labs Nashik, India

Lumos Student Representative

August 2022 - Current

- Connected 3+ Tier A colleges.
- · Conducted Quiz Nights and Fun Nights over Discord.
- Conducted 2 offline events of Web3 and Metaverse in College
- Technical Skills: Web3, Solidity, Block Chain
- · Soft Skills: Networking, Marketing, Team Management, Event Management

Cancer Foundation of India

Technical Intern

Nashik, India

• In a team we developed a website for Cancer Foundation of India

April 2022 - May 2022

- Interviewed Cancer Recovered Patients and collected their experence.
- Technical Skills: HTML, JavaScript, Css
- · Soft Skills: Public Speaking, Content Writing.

University Projects

Shop Management System

Nashik, India

Gokhale Education Society R.H. Sapat College of Engineering

Dec 2021 - June 2022

• For the Academic subject we created a Book Shop Management system in pure java code.

• Technical Skills: Java.

Skills_

Programming C, C++, CSS, HTML, Firebase, Javascript, Kotlin, Python.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Event Management, Public Speaking.

APRIL 14, 2023

2022 **Winner**, CSI Paper presentation

India

Languages _____

EnglishProfessional proficiencyHindiNative proficiencyMarathiNative proficiency

APRIL 14, 2023 2